<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My Life Files on Life Files</title><link>https://lieflike.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in My Life Files on Life Files</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 21:52:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lieflike.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I dont play video games anymore, alone</title><link>https://lieflike.github.io/posts/why-i-dont-play-video-games-anymore-alone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 21:52:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://lieflike.github.io/posts/why-i-dont-play-video-games-anymore-alone/</guid><description>TL;DR God-like skills to create your own game Mastery Humbleness This post means no intention of blasphemy, comparison or to offend anybody. I&amp;rsquo;ll make this short.
I used to be a big gamer which is what got me into tech. At the level of exposure I have to tech and the tech skill sets I&amp;rsquo;ve developed, I&amp;rsquo;d say that I now can create games. So this is what I feel when I play video games:</description></item><item><title>What to bring if you are invited to an Italian Dinner</title><link>https://lieflike.github.io/posts/what-to-bring-to-an-italian-dinner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 21:52:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://lieflike.github.io/posts/what-to-bring-to-an-italian-dinner/</guid><description>TL;DR Really good quality Olive Oil Nice wine I&amp;rsquo;m writing this story because this was my first invitation by an Italian friend to her house amongst a bunch of friends.
I did know what to bring that time. According to her, she was going to cook EVERYTHING and therefore, what could you bring?
Questions that arised were:
Will you go for something safe such as nice wine? Desserts and will this match the italian food she was about to prepare?</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://lieflike.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lieflike.github.io/about/</guid><description>I came from a huble town somewhere in the country of Europe.
I started travelling and hopping to different countries because of my job. A few years here and there.
I encountered a lot questions and things that are new to me like:
Basic things you need when camping (for camping first timers) What to do when bitten by a snake? How to pack for a 1 or 2 day out of town trip (camping or in an accommodation / with or without a car) Leaving the country you are at (with friends) Coming to a new country (to work for a few years) Got a plane ticket and leaving the country for good in a few days (With all your stuff at home still in their rightful place as if you were not leaving at all) I also share some personal stories which I do not even share with any of my friends.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://lieflike.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lieflike.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Thank you for your effort in reaching out and giving feedback, comments, complaints and suggestions!
Feel free to contact me using the form below. It should send it right to my email.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message Photo by Mathyas Kurmann on Unsplash</description></item></channel></rss>